{
    "subject": "resource/The_Secret_Garden_(1993_film)",
    "predicate": "property/gross",
    "object": "3.1181347E7",
    "human_readable": "The gross of the 1993 film 'The Secret Garden' is $31,181,347.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9520171880722046,
            "question": "What was the gross revenue of the 1993 film 'The Secret Garden'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8744994401931763,
            "question": "Was 'The Secret Garden' a profitable film in 1993?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8631527423858643,
            "question": "What is the financial performance of the 1993 film 'The Secret Garden'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6463444828987122,
            "question": "Could we compare the box office performance of 'The Secret Garden' to other films from 1993?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6306226849555969,
            "question": "How much money did 'The Secret Garden' make at the box office in 1993?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5994138717651367,
            "question": "What other films from 1993 had similar box office numbers to 'The Secret Garden'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5617603063583374,
            "question": "Approximately how successful was the film 'The Secret Garden' financially?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5026746392250061,
            "question": "Is there any information available about the budget of 'The Secret Garden'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2449992299079895,
            "question": "What factors might have contributed to the financial success (or lack thereof) of 'The Secret Garden'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.053236089646816254,
            "question": "Did the film's release year influence its box office performance?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The gross of the 1993 film 'The Secret Garden' is $31,181,347.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6968_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What factors might have contributed to the financial success (or lack thereof) of 'The Secret Garden'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6968_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there any information available about the budget of 'The Secret Garden'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6968_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Approximately how successful was the film 'The Secret Garden' financially?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6968_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6968_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6968_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6968_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6968_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6968_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6968_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6968_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6968_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6968_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6968_67.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports that the box office gross for the 1993 film \"The Secret Garden\" was $31,181,347."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}